Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 1 and District 1 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 1 Locals, 2.
  - Local 147
    - Local 147 Officers Lists, August 14, 1943-March 2, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Local 147 Incoming Correspondence, 1942-1945 (Box 9, Folder 138)
      - Julius Emspak to Harry Block Regarding Organization at Brubaker, September 25, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Gloria Travitz Regarding Finances, October 6, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Travitz Regarding Finances, February 10, 1942; 3.
      - Emspak to Emory Daniels Regarding Veterans and Finances, July 10, 1945; 4.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Travitz Regarding Local 147 Constitution, January 7, 1943; 5.
    - Local 147 Outgoing Correspondence, 1942-1949 (Box 9, Folder 139)
      - Harry Block to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization at Brubaker, September 28, 1942; 1.
      - Richard Brown to Emspak Regarding Disaffiliation and Anti-Communism, September 13, 1949; 2.
      - Emory Daniels to UE Regarding Veterans and Finances, July 10, 1945; 3.
      - Gloria Travitz to UE Regarding Local 147 Constitution, January 1943; 4.
      - Travitz to UE Regarding Supplies, April 1943; 5.
    - Local 147 Miscellaneous Finances, 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 140)
      - Charter, October 19, 1942; 1.
      - Bond Application, March 22, 1943; 2.
  - Local 148
    - Local 148 Officers Lists, April 5, 1943-September 5, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 141)
    - Local 148 Incoming Correspondence, 1943-1946 (Box 9, Folder 142)
      - Julius Emspak to Phillips Regarding Finances, March 24, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Robert Lewis Regarding Veterans and Finances, October 30, 1944; 2.
      - Emspak to Lewis Regarding Appointments, January 19, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Local 148 Financial Secretary Regarding Supplies, February 1945; 4.
      - Ray Klausner, Secretary of Emspak, to Joseph Clunk Regarding Mailing List, February 19, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to Edward Miller Regarding Finances, June 1, 1945; 6.
      - Emspak to Clunk Regarding Finances, Sepember 11, 1945; 7.
      - Emspak to Leo McCool Regarding Amalgamations, January 24, 1946; 8.
      - Emspak to Joseph Infante Regarding Mailing List, February 18, 1946; 9.
      - Emspak to Infante Regarding Finances, October 18, 1945; 10.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Lewis Regarding Local 148 Officers, September 1, 1944; 11.
    - Local 148 Outgoing Correspondence, 1944-1947 (Box 9, Folder 143)
      - Carl Bersing to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, April 14, 1944; 1.
      - Joseph Clunk to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 3, 1945; 2.
      - Clunk to UE Regarding Finances, July 30, 1947; 3.
      - Joseph Infante to Emspak Regarding Unemployment, February 21, 1946; 4.
      - Robert Lewis to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, October 17, 1944; 5-6.
      - Lewis to Emspak Regarding Appointments, January 12, 1945; 7.
      - Lewis to Emspak Regarding Local 148 Collective Bargaining, 8.
      - Lewis to Emspak Regarding Finances and War Labor Board with July 5, 1945, David Ratner Letter to Infante, June 25, 1945; 9.
      - Leo McCool to Emspak Regarding Finances with April 20, 1945, North Penn Weekly News Bill and June 14, 1945, Janet Barish Letter to Infante, June 5, 1945; 10.
      - McCool to Richard Davidson Regarding United Steelworkers Strike, October 30, 1945; 11.
      - McCool to Emspak Regarding Amalgamations and Organization at National Union Radio, January 14, 1946; 12.
    - Local 148 Per Capita Reports, August 10, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 144)
    - Local 148 Finances, Locals Receivable Ledger, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 145)
    - Local 148 Organization/Jurisdictional Dispute, 1943-1945 (Box 9, Folder 146)
      - Julius Emspak to Harry Block, March 24, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Carl Bersing, March 24, 1943; 2.
      - David McDonald to Albert Fitzgerald, May 12, 1943; 3.
      - Secretary of Fitzgerald to McDonald, May 14, 1943; 4.
      - Secretary of Fitzgerald to David Davis with May 12, 1943, McDonald Letter to Fitzgerald, May 14, 1943; 5.
      - Davis to Fitzgerald, May 25, 1943; 6.
      - Joseph Infante to Emspak, June 8, 1943; 7.
      - Emspak to Infante, June 9, 1943; 8.
      - Phillip Murray to Fitzgerald, August 7, 1943; 9.
      - Murray to Emspak with August 4, 1943, Michael Harris Letter to Murray, August 7, 1943; 10.
      - Secretary of Fitzgerald to Davis with August 7, 1943, Murray Letter to Fitzgerald and August 4, 1943, Harris Letter to Murray, August 10, 1943; 11.
      - Secretary of Fitzgerald to Murray, August 11, 1943; 12.
      - Bersing to Fitzgerald with Summary of Activity, August 19, 1943; 13.
      - Bersing to Fitzgerald, August 20, 1943; 14.
      - Harris to Fitzgerald, August 20, 1943; 15.
      - Bersing to Emspak, March 7, 1944; 16.
      - Peter Besch to James Matles, October 31, 1945; 17.
    - Local 148 Disbanding, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 147)
      - Report from David Ratner, February 25, 1947; 1.
      - Murray Portnoy to Ratner, July 8, 1947; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Portnoy, July 17, 1947; 3.
    - Local 148 Miscellaneous, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 148)
      - Union's Proposals on General Wage Adjustments, 1943; 1.
      - Minutes of Grievance Meetings, July 31-August 31, 1944; 2.
    - Local 148 Company Magazine, The SKF Sphere with February 27, 1945, Joseph Infante Letter to Julius Emspak, March 1, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 149)
    - Local 148 Newspaper Clippings, North Penn Reporter with June 1, 1944, Joseph Infante Letter to Julius Emspak, May 23, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 150)
  - Local 149
    - Local 149 Officers Lists, January 29, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 151)
    - Local 149 Incoming Correspondence, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 152)
      - Secretary of Julius Emspak to Murray Portnoy Regarding Organization at Western Electric in Allentown, January 28, 1948; 1.
      - Ray Klausner, Secretary of Emspak, to Portnoy Regarding Supplies, February 3, 1948; 2.
      - Emspak to Portnoy Regarding Finances and Supplies, February 16, 1948; 3.
      - Emspak to James Price Regarding Organization at Western Electric in Allentown, February 16, 1948; 4.
      - Emspak to Eugene Petryk Regarding Supplies, February 16, 1948; 5.
    - Local 149 Outgoing Correspondence, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 153)
      - Eugene Petryk to James Matles Regarding Organization at Western Electric in Allentown, February 27, 1948; 1.
      - Petryk to Matles Regarding Address Change, April 20, 1948; 2.
      - Petryk to Julius Emspak Regarding Address Change, April 20, 1948; 3.
      - Murray Portnoy to Emspak Regarding Veterans and Finances, February 3, 1948; 4.
      - William Thamel to Emspak Regarding Organization at Western Electric in Allentown, December 2, 1948; 5.
    - Local 149 Miscellaneous Financial, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 154)
      - Charter Supplies, January 29, 1948; 1.
      - Locals Receivable Ledger, January 29, 1948; 2.
  - Local 150
    - Local 150 Officers Lists, March 9-April 28, 1948, undated (Box 9, Folder 155)
    - Local 150 Incoming Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 156)
      - Julius Emspak to Henry Rhine Regarding Organization at Electric Service Manufacturing, March 15, 1948; 1.
      - Emspak to James Price Regarding Supplies, March 15, 1948; 2.
      - Emspak to John MacEwan Regarding Supplies, March 15, 1948; 3.
      - Emspak to Joseph Rock Regarding Local 150 Officers, April 27, 1948; 4.
      - Emspak to Ernest DeBellis Regarding Local 150 Strike at Electric Service Manufacturing, June 4, 1948; 5.
      - Emspak to Fred Stoerrle Regarding Local 150 Officers, March 23, 1949; 6.
    - Local 150 Outgoing Correspondence, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 157)
      - Ernest DeBellis to Julius Emspak Regarding Local 150 Strike at Electric Service Manufacturing, June 9, 1948; 1.
      - James Price to Emspak Regarding Local 150 Strike and Organization at Electric Service Manufacturing, March 5, 1948; 2.
      - Price to Emspak Regarding Local 150 Strike at Electric Service Manufacturing, May 24, 1948; 3.
      - Abraham Ruzansky to Emspak Regarding Supplies, April 28, 1948; 4.
      - Ruzansky to Emspak Regarding Local 150 Strike at Electric Service Manufacturing and Finances, August 5, 1948; 5.
      - Joseph Rock to Emspak Regarding Supplies, April 26, 1948; 6.
      - Fred Stoerrle to Emspak Regarding Local 150 Strike at Electric Service Manufacturing and Supplies, April 21, 1948; 7.
    - Local 150 Miscellaneous Finances, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 158)
      - Charter Supplies, March 9, 1948; 1.
      - Locals Receivable Ledger, March 9, 1948; 2.
  - Local 151
    - Local 151 Officers Lists, March 11, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 159)
    - Local 151 Incoming Correspondence, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 160)
      - Julius Emspak to Jack Myers Regarding Organization at Monroe Calculating in Bristol, March 17, 1948; 1.
      - Emspak to Myers Regarding Organization at Monroe Calculating in Bristol, March 18, 1948; 2.
      - Emspak to James Price Regarding Organization at Monroe Calculating in Bristol, March 29, 1948; 3.
      - Emspak to Myers Regarding Organization at Monroe Calculating in Bristol, March 29, 1948; 4.
      - Emspak to Claude Covett Regarding Organization at Monroe Calculating in Bristol, March 29, 1948; 5.
      - Emspak to Myers Regarding Mailing List, April 14, 1948; 6.
      - Emspak to Roy Wells Regarding Organization at Monroe Calculating in Bristol, April 27, 1948; 7.
    - Local 151 Outgoing Correspondence, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 161)
      - Jack Myers to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization at Monroe Calculating in Bristol, March 11, 1948; 1.
      - Myers to Emspak Regarding Organization at Monroe Calculating in Bristol, April 2, 1948; 2.
      - Henry Rhine to James Matles Regarding Organization at Monroe Calculating in Bristol and Inter-union Rivalry with the International Association of Machinists, March 16, 1948; 3.
      - Joseph Tipton to Emspak Regarding Organization at Monroe Calculating in Bristol, March 11, 1948; 4.
    - Local 151 Miscellaneous Financial, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 162)
      - Local 151 Charter Supplies, March 11, 1948; 1.
      - Locals Receivable Ledger, March 11, 1948; 2.
  - Local 155
    - Local 155 Officer Lists, 1941-February 11, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 163)
    - Local 155 General Incoming Correspondence, 1938-1954 (Box 9, Folder 164)
      - Janet Barish to Francis White Regarding Staff Finances, November 8, 1943; 1.
      - Barish to Harriet Fahey Regarding Finances, May 15, 1947; 2.
      - Barish to Max Helfand Regarding Staff Finances, February 21, 1951; 3.
      - Barish to Thomas Delaney Regarding Staff Finances, March 20, 1952; 4.
      - Barish to Charles Fluher Regarding Staff Finances, June 23, 1952; 5.
      - Barish to John Baumgardner Regarding Finances with September 1, 1952, Statement, September 3, 1952; 6.
      - Barish to Baumgardner Regarding Staff Finances, September 11, 1952; 7.
      - Barish to Fahey Regarding Staff Finances, January 30, 1953; 8.
      - Peter Besch to Helfand Regarding Local 155 Strike at H.S. Getty with Letter to James Matles, January 29, 1946; 9.
      - Harry Block to Helfmand Regarding Local 155 Strike at H.S. Getty, January 11, 1946; 10.
      - William Cahn to Helen Laughlin Regarding Office of Price Administration and Radio Broadcasts, July 22, 1946; 11.
      - Cahn to Laughlin Regarding Nathan Report and Political Action, January 23, 1947; 12.
      - Cahn to Helfand Regarding Stewards Training, February 4, 1949; 13.
      - Cahn to White Regarding Publicity, April 4, 1951; 14.
      - Lewis Clark to Charles Smith Regarding United Packinghouse Workers Strike, April 13, 1949; 15.
      - Julius Emspak to J.P. Gallagher Regarding Finances, October 28, 1938; 16.
      - Emspak to Gallagher Regarding Supplies, January 30, 1939; 17.
      - Emspak to William Winters Regarding Supplies, March 16, 1939; 18.
      - Emspak to Winters Regarding Supplies, April 17, 1939; 19.
      - Emspak to Winters Regarding Finances, May 3, 1939; 20.
      - Emspak to Winters Regarding Local 155 Strike, June 15, 1939; 21.
      - Emspak to Local 155 Regarding Finances, June 26, 1939; 22.
      - Emspak to Winters Regarding Finances, August 4, 1939; 23.
      - Emspak to Winters Regarding Finances, September 5, 1939; 24.
      - Emspak to Winters Regarding Supplies and Unemployment, April 12, 1940; 25.
      - Emspak to Winters Regarding Finances, April 12, 1940; 26.
      - Emspak to Winters Regarding Finances, April 30, 1940; 27.
      - Emspak to Winters Regarding Supplies, July 11, 1940; 28.
      - Emspak to Winters Regarding Mailing List, September 26, 1940; 29-30.
      - Emspak to Winters Regarding Mailing List, October 18, 1940; 31.
      - Emspak to J.J. Houghton Regarding Local 155 Annual Ball, December 6, 1940; 32.
      - Emspak to Edward Worthington Regarding Local 155 Officers, January 8, 1941; 33.
      - Emspak to William Williams Regarding Mailing List, February 3, 1941; 34.
      - Emspak to Worthington Regarding Supplies, April 24, 1941; 35.
      - Emspak to Worthington Regarding C.S. Jackson Case, November 1, 1941; 36.
      - Emspak to White Regarding Local 155 Annual Ball, November 26, 1941; 37.
      - Emspak to Worthington Regarding Mine, Mill & Smelter Workers Stike in Kirkland Lake, February 19, 1942; 38.
      - Emspak to Worthington Regarding Factionalism, August 31, 1942; 39.
      - Emspak to White Regarding Staff Finances, March 1, 1943; 40.
      - Emspak to Fahey Regarding Miami, April 27, 1943; 41.
      - Emspak to White Regarding Staff Finances, May 12, 1943; 42.
      - Emspak to Philip Saba Regarding CIO News, May 18, 1943; 43.
      - Emspak to White Regarding Organization at Gosa, Brockman & Mitchell Specialities, May 20, 1943; 44.
      - Emspak to White with July 12, 1943, Mrs. William Wray Letter to UE, July 14, 1943; 45.
      - Emspak to Harry Block Regarding Transfer of CIO Local 114, August 28, 1943; 46.
      - Emspak to Joseph Walter Regarding Organization at Bendix and Staff Members with November 15, 1943, Emspak Letter to White, November 5, 1943; 47.
      - Emspak to Edward Larkin Regarding Finances, November 15, 1943; 48.
      - Emspak to Larkin Regarding Finances, December 2, 1943; 49.
      - Emspak to Larkin Regarding Finances, December 10, 1943; 50.
      - Emspak to Fahey Regarding Finances, February 3, 1944; 51.
      - Emspak to Fahey Regarding Finances, March 7, 1944; 52.
      - Emspak to White Regarding David Davis Testemonial Dinner, March 29, 1944; 53.
      - Emspak to Fahey Regarding Finances, April 4, 1944; 54.
      - Emspak to Fahey Regarding Finances, May 4, 1944; 55.
      - Emspak to Larkin Regarding Veterans and Finances, May 5, 1944; 56.
      - Emspak to Fahey Regarding Finances, June 1, 1944; 57.
      - Emspak to Fahey Regarding Finances, October 17, 1944; 58.
      - Emspak to Fahey Regarding Staff Members, March 7, 1945; 59.
      - Emspak to Gaylord LeRoy Regarding Staff Finances, March 16, 1945; 60.
      - Emspak to Harry Doriss Regarding Afro-Americans, January 5, 1946; 61.
      - Emspak to Laughlin Regarding Local 155 Stewards Banquet, January 5, 1946; 62.
      - Emspak to Helfand Regarding Local 155 Strike at H.S. Getty, January 16, 1946; 63.
      - Emspak to Laughlin Regarding Local 155 Officers, January 24, 1946; 64.
      - Emspak to Local 155 Public Affairs Committee Regarding Supplies, March 11, 1946; 65.
      - Emspak to Joseph Brown Regarding Veterans and Finances, June 25, 1946; 66.
      - Emspak Telegram to White Regarding Local 155 Strike at Proctor Electric, October 28, 1946; 67.
      - Emspak to Laughlin Regarding PAC, November 20, 1946; 68.
      - Emspak to Laughlin Regarding PAC, January 7, 1948; 69.
      - Emspak to Hellman Regarding Appointments, March 24, 1948; 70.
      - Emspak to Charles Fluher Regarding Local 155 Strike at American Pulley Company, July 13, 1948; 71.
      - Emspak to Brown Regarding Finances, October 7, 1948; 72.
      - Emspak to Fuher Regarding Staff Finances, December 15, 1948; 73.
      - Secretary of Emspak to Laughlin Regarding Local 155 Anniversary Ball, May 2, 1949; 74.
      - Emspak to Marc Gaylburd Regarding Taft-Hartley and Non-Communist Affidavits, November 28, 1949; 75.
      - Secretary of Emspak to Francis Wilkinson Regarding Finances, May 15, 1950; 76.
      - Emspak to Donald Ferguson Regarding Local 155 Banquet, May 16, 1952; 77.
      - Emspak to Fluher Regarding Finances, August 14, 1952; 78.
      - Emspak to Fluher Regarding Inter-union Rivalry and Finances, August 29, 1952; 79.
      - Emspak to Baumgardner Regarding Finances, March 13, 1953; 80.
      - Emspak to Baumgardner Regarding Finances, March 25, 1953; 81.
      - Emspak to Baumgardner Regarding Finances, April 21, 1953; 82.
      - Emspak to Baumgardner Regarding Finances, May 26, 1953; 83.
      - Emspak to Baumgardner Regarding Finances, June 25, 1953; 84.
      - Emspak to Baumgardner Regarding Finances, August 6, 1953; 85.
      - Emspak to Fluher Regarding Finances, January 13, 1954; 86.
      - Emspak to John Kleppy Regarding Finances with January 12, 1953, Statements, January 14, 1954; 87.
      - Emspak to Kleppy Regarding Finances with Statement, May 10, 1954; 88.
      - Emspak to Kleppy Regarding Finances with July 22 and July 7, 1954, Statements, 89.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to White Regarding Local 155 Annual Ball, November 28, 1941; 90.
      - Fitzgerald to White Regarding David Davis Testimonial Dinner, March 28, 1944; 91.
      - Fitzgerald to Delaney Regarding Nicholson File, September 24, 1945; 92.
      - Secretary of Fitzgerald to Laughlin Regarding Local 155 Stewards Banquet, December 26, 1945; 93.
      - Fitzgerald to Laughlin Regarding Local 155 Stewards Banquet, January 10, 1946; 94.
      - Secretary of Fitzgerald to Dillon Stewart, October 24, 1946; 95.
      - Fitzgerald to Laughlin Regarding Local 155 Stewards Banquet, January 6, 1947; 96.
      - Secretary of Fitzgerald to Laughlin Regarding Local 155 Stewards Banquet, January 20, 1948; 97.
      - Secretary of Fitzgerald to Laughlin Regarding Local 155 Stewards Banquet, January 20, 1948; 98.
      - Fitzgerald to Ferguson Regarding Local 155 Annual Banquet, May 16, 1952; 99.
      - Augustine Gisondi to Fluher Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry with a Letter to Fitzgerald, August 14, 1952; 100.
      - John Gojack to White Regarding Organization at Aircraft Products in Fort Wayne and Local 155 Contract at Eby with a Letter to Emspak and August 27, 1943, Emspak Response, August 19, 1943; 101.
      - Gojack to White Regarding Wages, Hugh Eby, and Aircrafts Products in Fort Wayne, August 26, 1943; 102.
      - Gojack Telegram to White Regarding Contracts at Aircraft Products, November 11, 1943; 103.
      - Clifford McAvoy to Laughlin Regarding Political Action, February 6, 1947; 104.
      - McAvoy to Laughlin Regarding Reservations, March 26, 1947; 105.
      - James Matles to Houghton Regarding Local 155 Annual Ball, December 11, 1940; 106.
      - Matles to Worthington Regarding Local 155 Annual Ball, January 3, 1941; 107.
      - Secretary of Matles to White Regarding Local 155 Annual Ball, November 19, 1941; 108.
      - Matles to Worthington Regarding Finances, March 23, 1943; 109.
      - Matles to White Regarding Local 155 Annual Ball, February 9, 1943; 110.
      - Matles to Ann Vergil Regarding Local 155 Executive Board Meeting, February 15, 1943; 111.
      - Matles to Larkin Regarding Local 155 Executive Board Meeting, March 1, 1943; 112.
      - Matles to Larkin Regarding Staff Members, March 23, 1943; 113.
      - Matles to White Regarding Fort Wayne, May 6, 1943; 114.
      - Secretary of Matles Telegram to White, July 2, 1943; 115.
      - Matles to White Regarding Staff Members, August 9, 1943; 116.
      - Matles to Laughlin Regarding Local 155 Stewards Banquet, January 3, 1946; 117.
      - Matles to Laughlin Regarding Membership Meeting, November 25, 1946; 118.
      - Matles to Ferguson Regarding Local 155 Annual Ball, May 20, 1947; 119.
      - Matles to Laughlin Regarding Taft-Hartley and Claude Pepper, January 6, 1948; 120.
      - Matles to Laughlin Regarding Local 155 Stewards Banquet, January 23, 1948; 121.
      - Matles to Laughlin Regarding Local 155 Stewards Banquet, January 28, 1949; 122.
      - Matles to Laughlin Regarding Local 155 Annual Ball, May 4, 1949; 123.
      - Matles to C.D. Fowler Regarding Staff Finances, June 13, 1952; 124.
      - Matles to Fluher Regarding House Un-American Activities Committee, October 30, 1952; 125.
      - Secretary of Matles to McCann, March 22, 1954; 126.
      - Matles to Helfand Regarding Employment and A.O. Smith, August 5, 1955; 127.
      - Russ Nixon to Laughlin Regarding PAC, November 3, 1947; 128.
      - Basil Pollitt to Helfand Regarding Guards, January 6, 1954; 129.
      - David Ratner to Laughlin Regarding Staff Members, January 3, 1945; 130.
      - Ratner to Fahey Regarding Supplies, May 31, 1946; 131.
      - Ratner to Fahey, October 12, 1946; 132.
      - Ratner to Fahey Regarding Appointments, November 4, 1946; 133.
      - Ratner to Fahey Regarding Supplies, May 23, 1947; 134.
      - Ratner to Helfmand Regarding Staff Finances, March 13, 1950; 135.
      - Ratner to Delaney Regarding Staff Finances, March 27, 1950; 136.
      - Ratner to Delaney Regarding Staff Finances, April 14, 1950; 137.
      - Nat Spero to Gaylord Le Roy Regarding Wages at Decca Record, July 10, 1944; 138.
      - Louis Wallen to Delaney Regarding Factionalism, May 25, 1952; 139.
    - Local 155 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1938-1955 (Box 9, Folder 165)
      - John Baumgardner to Julius Emspak Regarding UE Fighting Fund and Finances, July 15, 1952; 1.
      - Baumgardner to James Matles Regarding Staff Finances, September 10, 1952; 2.
      - Baumgardner to Emspak Regarding Strike at International Harvester, December 4, 1952; 3.
      - Baumgardner to Emspak Regarding Strike at International Harvester, December 31, 1952; 4.
      - Baumgardner to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 19, 1953; 5.
      - Baumgardner to Emspak Regarding UE Fighting Fund, April 8, 1953; 6.
      - Baumgardner to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 17, 1953; 7.
      - Baumgardner to Emspak Regarding Finances with May 15, 1953, Statements, May 8, 1953; 8.
      - Baumgardner to Emspak Regarding Finances, May 21, 1953; 9.
      - Baumgardner to Emspak Regarding Finances with Statement, June 8, 1953; 10.
      - Baumgardner to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 25, 1953; 11.
      - Harry Block to Emspak Regarding Local 119 Transfers, August 11, 1943; 12.
      - Joseph Brown Regarding Veterans and Finances, June 20, 1946; 13.
      - Brown to Emspak Regarding Local 155 Strike at William Sellers, August 20, 1946; 14.
      - Brown to Emspak Regarding Finances, September 30, 1948; 15.
      - Brown to Emspak Regarding Finances, October 11, 1948; 16.
      - Brown to Emspak Regarding United Packinghouse Workers Strike, March 23, 1949; 17.
      - Brown to Emspak Regarding Local 155 Strike with Receipt, July 22, 1949; 18.
      - Edward DeBuest to Matles Regarding Finances, March 15, 1950; 19.
      - DeBuest to Emspak Regarding Political Action and 1944 Split, December 6, 1950; 20.
      - DeBuest to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding UE Fighting Fund, November 9, 1951; 21.
      - DeBuest to Emspak Regarding Wage Conference, March 21, 1952; 22.
      - DeBuest to Emspak Regarding Strike at International Harvester, November 5, 1952; 23.
      - DeBuest to David Ratner Regarding Finances with November 20, 1952, Statement, November 12, 1952; 24.
      - DeBuest to Dwight Eisenhower Regarding Communist Control Act and Mine, Mill & Smelter Workers with August 2, 1955, Resolution, August 5, 1955; 25.
      - Thomas Delaney to Emspak Regarding Local 155 Strike at Nicholson File and Smith Connally, September 20, 1945; 26.